http://github.com/cvhu

## **Objective**

I enjoy building trust with people and making a meaningful impact, and I love solving complex problems with simple yet elegant solutions.

10 years of experience in software engineering for API integration, architecture design, full-stack feature development. 5 years of experience in leading projects and growing engineers.

# Experiences

# Senior Software Engineer at Panopto

Jan 2020 - Present

Designed and implemented both Microsoft Teams and Cisco WebEx Meetings integration features from the ground up, including automatic recording imports, in-app extensions, and support tooling. Acted as the tech lead to collaborate with external partners, internal stakeholders, and mentor engineers. Tech Stack: C#, React(TypeScript),  $AWS\ Lambda(Python)$ , DynamoDB.

## Engineering Lead at Indeed.com

May 2014 - Jan 2020

Engineering Manager, Profile (Jul 2019 to Jan 2020): Managing a team of 4 software engineers. Building intervention solutions for low-quality job applications. Promoted 1 engineer and received 100% satisfaction ratings from all direct reports for 2 consecutive quarters.

Tech Lead, Profile (Oct 2017 to Jul 2019):

Resume Delivery Platform, Context Fields, Dashboard, and Modernized UI. Team lead for 4 full-time engineers, mentored 7 industry hires, interviewed 100+ senior engineer candidates. Promoted to level 3. Tech Stack: Java Spring MVC, React, Redux, Webpack, MongoDB, Datadog, Docker, PagerDuty, Jenkins, JIRA.

Engineering Lead, Indeed University (Jul to Sep 2017):

Technical advisor for 2 product teams, manager-in-practice for 5 new engineers.

Software Engineer, Targeted Ads (Apr 2016 to Jun 2017):

Ad placement and delivery, conversion tracking, and support tools. Mentored 6 full-time engineers. Interviewed 100+ engineering candidates. Promoted to level 2.

Softare Engineer, Job Search (May 2014 to Mar 2016):

User data deletion platform, CSS style guide v0, 3rd-party conversion tracking, and search result A/B tests. Programming exercise trainer and contributor.

# Co-founder at Dediced.com

Jun 2011 - Dec 2015

Sole tech contributor for a full-stack Ruby On Rails + jQuery app for bookmark storage, recommendation engine, and searching.

# Software Engineer at IBM Corp.

May 2013 - May 2014

- \* Developed features and tools for a BPM webapp with GWT (Java) and Maven.
- $\star$  Communicated with customers to fully automate their common tasks.
- $\star$  Delivered code on both front-end and back-end to thousands of clients worldwide.

## First Employee at Souplus Inc.

Feb-Dec 2012

First engineer hired to build 4 prototypes for a startup from scratch, including a groupon-like tool for restaurant owners, a yelp-like gaming platform with collaborative filtering, a location-based mileage competition iOS app, and a task management system with handshake protocols.

#### Education

### University of Texas at Austin

Sep 2012 - Dec 2013

MS in Software Engineering

 $\label{lem:course} \mbox{Course Highlights: Concurrent \& Distributed Computing, Data Mining, Reinforcement Learning, Natural Language Processing}$ 

Rice University

Sep 2007 - May 2011

Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering, Cum Laude Bachelor of Arts in Physics, Cum Laude